Cameronbiega@gmail.com

Cameron Down

20 Vaisey Close Kariong NSW 2250

Website: https://caminusprime.github.io/Cameron.github.io/Cameron.github.io/ LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/cameron.github.io/ Cameron.github.io/

SKILLS

Programming consistently since 2017 with experience in **C**, **C++**, **C#**, **JavaScript**, **HTML**, **CSS**, and **SQL** with focus on a variety of projects from console, desktop, and mobile applications as well as webpage development work and hardware level integration utilizing libraries such as **HTML Canvas**, **.NET Maui** and **ASP.NET MVC** tools.

Experience within the **Adobe suite** since 2013 and similar software packages to create a variety of media mainly focusing on Photo and Video creation. Additional experience with the **Microsoft office suite**.

Experience with **Git Bash** to maintain projects collaboratively. Experienced in reading source documentation to learn new skills and integrate into projects.

INTERESTS

Large interest in 3D modelling, 3D printing, Games design and Costume building.

I apply a variety of skills to recreate items from media including games and movies as wearable costume pieces. I've applied skills I've learned to make a number of costumes originally in fiberglass hand made pieces to now fully 3D modelled and printed pieces using a variety of techniques to get from digital models to completely wearable high quality physical pieces. This can include electronic work in the form of programming in C++ and circuitry to integrate effects.

Another interest of mine is working with game design and development in the unreal game engine.

EXPERIENCE

12/2018 - Present

Team Member, Officeworks – West Gosford, NSW

- Customer service role in technology, stationery and print departments.
- Use of skills and knowledge to assist customers with their tech needs ranging from computer hardware, monitors, printers, POS systems to networking and more.
- Working flexibly through tasks in a high demand situation
- Adapting to different situations when necessary, such as providing assistance within different departments including POS, print copy and create or stationary departments if those areas encounter issues.
- Diagnosing issues with hardware and software to rectify or process as necessary within the company's parameters.

9/2019 - 12/2021

Team Member, Toymate - Erina Fair, NSW

- Participated in creating training purpose videos for new staff members.
- Aiding in the construction of new store fixtures and setup

8/2016 - 8/2018

Team Member, Toys R Us - Erina Fair, NSW

- Customer service experience within stressful time periods
- Grand opening events maintaining large crowds.
- Use of database systems
- Preparing for events for items including display signage or stock counts required

6/2014 - 12/2016

Stock Processor, GeoDiscoveries - West Gosford, NSW

- Database management systems and processing invoices through MYOB
- Creating packaging for fragile objects of various sizes and detailed labels including necessary information.
- Stock processing and inventory catalog for client orders.

EDUCATION

2/2019 - 11/2023

Graduated Bachelor of Information Technology Majoring in Systems development – University of Newcastle.

- Programming experience with HTML, Java, C & C# with applied learning for the development of console, web, and mobile applications.
- Understanding of networking devices, protocols, and systems
- Game design and development experience within unreal engine and unity.
- Adobe application experience with applications including photoshop, Dreamweaver, Audition, and illustrator.
- Experience with User-Interface development for Augmented and virtual reality interfaces.
- Professional practice within IT and project management.

2/2017 - 10/2018

Bachelor of Engineering Mechatronics – University of Newcastle

• incomplete however experience here included engineering-based 3D modelling for measurement orientated design as well as sustainable resource considerations for projects and working with programming Arduino devices for robotics purposes.

2/2016 - 12/2016 6/2013 - 12/2013 Newstep course - University of Newcastle

Cert II in information, digital media, and technology ICA20111 – Academy of interactive entertainment (AIE)

2/2010 - 12/2015

• Experience with C# developing 2D application for games

Completed Year 12 High School Certificate – Kariong Mountains High school.

 Completed HSC with experience Information processing technology outlining the various processed involved in developing, improving, or maintaining systems within a business environment as well as Design and technology understanding the concepts behind ergonomic or user-friendly design.

REFERENCES

Details upon request

Tanya McBride Context: Prev. Manager Officeworks west Gosford Dr. Donald Brooker Context: Teacher, Kariong Mountains High school Jacqueline Bailey Context: Course coordinator, University of Newcastle